sprysoft.com 2008-06-23

# Sprysoft Academic Software, Student Software Discounts

Sprysoft knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Sprysoft, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice. 

**What Personal Information About Customers Does Sprysoft Gather?**

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Sprysoft. Here are the types of information we gather:

  * Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other ways. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as communicating with you, customizing the shopping experience for you, responding to your requests, and improving our site.   

  * Eligibility Information: For many products purchased from Sprysoft, we are required to collect proof of Academic eligibility. This may include a copy of your Academic ID, Driver’s License, proof of enrollment, etc.  

  * Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use cookies, and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Sprysoft.  

  * E-mail Communications: To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we may receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Sprysoft if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers.  

  * Information from Other Sources: For reasons such as improving personalization of our service (for example, providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. We also sometimes receive updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.   

**What About Cookies?**  

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide special features and storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.   

  * The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to shop at Sprysoft, and we recommend that you leave them turned on.   

**Does Sprysoft Share the Information It Receives?**  

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only with the subsidiaries Sprysoft Corporation controls and as described below. 

  * Suppliers: Sprysoft may allow our suppliers from time to time to verify that the software that we sold you was going to an Academically eligible party. These documents will not leave Sprysoft premises and they will not be used for marketing purposes by any other company.  

  * Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control: We work closely with our affiliated businesses. In some cases, these businesses operate stores linked from Sprysoft or sell offerings to you at Sprysoft. In other cases, we operate stores, provide services, or sell product lines jointly with these businesses.  

  * Agents: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.   

  * Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that Sprysoft Corporation or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.   

  * Protection of Sprysoft and Others: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law or protect the rights, property, or safety of Sprysoft, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.   

  * With Your Consent: Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.   

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**  

  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.   

  * We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.   

  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.   

**What Information Can I Access?**

Sprysoft gives you access to Your Account for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. Additional access may be added as our Web site evolves.

 **What Choices Do I Have?**

  * As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of Sprysoft features 
  * You can add or update certain information on pages mentioned in the "What Information Can I Access?" section above. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records. 
  * The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, you will not be able to shop at Sprysoft without enabling these features. 

In addition, the Federal Trade Commission provides useful information about online privacy on its own Web site, Site Seeing on the Internet. 

**Children**

Sprysoft does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use Sprysoft only with involvement of a parent or guardian. 

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

If you choose to visit Sprysoft, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Delaware. If you have any concern about privacy at Sprysoft, please send us a thorough description to [service@sprysoft.com](mailto:service@sprysoft.com), and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This notice will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. 

**Information You Give Us**

You provide most such information when you search, buy, bid, post, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you search for a product; provide information in Your Account (and you might have more than one if you have used more than one e-mail address when shopping with us); upload, fax or email eligibility documents; communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire or a contest entry form; compile Wish Lists; submit a rebate form; enter a shopping Community by providing employer, school, or other such information; participate in Discussion Boards; provide and rate Reviews; and employ other Personal Notification Services "Sprysoft Deals," and "Sprysoft Alerts". As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone number; credit card information; people to whom purchases have been shipped, including address and phone number; people (with addresses and phone numbers) listed in settings; e-mail addresses; content of reviews and e-mails to us; personal description and photograph; and financial information, including Social Security and driver's license numbers. 

**Automatic Information**

Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for; and phone number used to call our 800 number.
